The duel between the queen, Claire Harvey,
and the new student,
Kisaragi Hayato, shall begin.
Kisaragi-kun is doing this for us...
Please don't get yourself hurt...
I will explain the rules.
The time limit will be fifteen minutes.
The match will end when
a combatant is knocked out,
or when their energy runs out
and they're disarmed.
Liddy, I would like
to declare one thing here.
What is it?
I will not use full-body
armament in this duel.
Full-body armament?
A fighting tactic that only
a few people at this school can use.
It releases a weapon's energy all at once
and allows the wielder to use its full capabilities.
The fight would be over in a second,
and that wouldn't be fair
to our audience today.
She's saying she's going to hold back.
Emile?
I'll act as your support, so don't worry.
Use our plan to win, Hayato.
Kisaragi Hayato,
it's against the rules to
receive help during a duel.
I don't mind, Erica.
He's a new student here.
I'll permit it as a handicap.
Ten...
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Now, Kisaragi Hayato,
Six...
Five...
show me how strong you are!
Four...
Three...
I have no choice.
Two...
One...
Hayato!
Claire-sama!
Ow...
Huh?
The Invincible Queen
J-J-Just
wh-where do you think you're touching?!
Huh?
S-Sorry! I'm still not able to control
my powers that well.
Could you forgive me...
Not likely, huh?
Of course I won't!
I've never had anyone
touch my ch-chest before.
And you...
h-had the gall to fondle me?!
Aliceterion!
Energy barrier!
It seems you're at least
a little bit capable.
Thanks, Emile.
Why did you have to grab
the president's boobs?!
It wasn't on purpose!
Why are you getting mad?
Well, whatever.
We failed with our initial plan,
but our plan of attack isn't incorrect.
Try to charge in again, Hayato.
Got it.
Is that all you've got?
Damn it!
Hayato, use the other move.
Right.
What's that?
What is he doing?
All that training wasn't for nothing.
All right!
That was more than I expected,
Kisaragi Hayato.
It was worth trying.
However, this is the finale!
Hayato!
Kisaragi-san!
Kisaragi-kun!
I think we can see
the outcome of this fight.
Do you give up?
N-Not yet.
Hayato...
That's the spirit. And
I shall respond in kind!
The Buster Cannon?
She's going to use it against a new student?
This is bad!
You can't, Hayato!
Hayato! Hayato!
What is going on?
Can you hear me, Hayato?!
My body's so hot...
This is the end, Kisaragi Hayato.
Wh-What's going on...
His movements have changed.
The president is being pushed back.
Oh?
But at this distance...
A full-body armament...
And he's deploying an N-Barrier...
That can't be.
Kisaragi Hayato has only had
his Hundred for two days!
He's fast!
Claire-sama!
I am the perfect queen.
I can't lose here!
Petal.
Hayato!
This is the end,
Kisaragi Hayato!
Hayato!
Thank goodness...
What are you trying to pull?
You said you weren't going to use
your full-body armament!
Hold on a second, Emile.
The declaration she made
had nothing to do with the rules of a duel.
Char...
I know what you want to say,
but this match was won by Claire Harvey.
No, I lost here.
Even if I won under the rules,
I lost to myself.
Then how about we leave it
as a tie in the official record?
Where... am I?
I...
Hayato... Hayato...
Who is that?
I'm sorry...
Hayato.
Have you come to?
President...?
I see... I lost.
Then Emile and the girls
are still getting expelled?
I canceled the order.
Huh?
I see...
I don't remember anything
from halfway through.
Kisaragi Hayato...
Just who are you?
H-Huh?
In your first duel,
you used a full-body armament,
and deployed an N-Barrier.
You managed to corner me, the queen.
That shouldn't normally be possible.
What's going on?
I-I don't know, either...
Hayato!
What's the meaning of this, President?
Are you still trying to do
something to Hayato?!
Hey, Emile.
I just came to apologize.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Hmph!
Hayato, are you okay?
Yeah. Sorry for making you worry.
No, no. I'm just glad you're okay.
Please don't let it get you down.
If it had been a normal duel,
you would have won hands down.
That's not what I'm thinking about.
Th-Then are you
bothered by the fact that you
had your b-b-boobs touched?
Wh—?
That wasn't anything!
Erica,
Claire-sama isn't someone to get worked up
because someone grabbed her boobs.
Yeah, but Liddy,
even I haven't touched Claire-sama's
sublime boobs for myself.
Th-That's enough about boobs!
S-Sorry.
Yep. It looks like you're fine now.
You worry too much.
I'm fine.
I'm pretty hungry, though.
Here you go.
Oh, thanks.
When you use a lot of energy,
you get hungry, supposedly.
I see.
Hey, Hayato, do you want to go to Central?
We have today off.
Central?
It's the Little Garden's business district.
I'm sure there are a lot of places to eat.
Yeah. Sounds good.
Yay!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Did you really want to go Central that badly?
That's not it! I wanted to go on
a date with you that badly!
I see. So this is Central.
You wouldn't think we were on a ship.
Hey, Emile?
Are we kind of standing out for some reason?
It's not us, it's you.
Everyone was watching yesterday's duel.
Seriously?
Anyway, Hayato.
Here you go. Open up.
Wh-Why?
Come on.
How is it?
It's pretty good, I guess.
I know, right?
I'll have some of yours, too.
H-Hey!
Yum! Strawberry's pretty good!
You know...
Kisaragi-kun and Crossfode-kun
are pretty close.
Kind of makes you wonder, huh?
They're in the same dorm room, right?
Wow!
Hey, Emile, let's go get some food.
A-Anywhere will do.
Sure, but before that,
there's one place I want to go.
Wow!
Cool, isn't it, Hayato?
Yeah, but...
Hm?
This is unmistakably a date spot, isn't it?
I wanted to come here with you.
I heard it had a
great view of the ocean.
Wh-What?
Nothing.
Nothing, really.
Apparently it gets even more
romantic at sundown.
I... I see.
Your sister?
Y-Yeah.
Hello?
Nii-san, why didn't you tell me
about the duel?
Sorry. I just didn't want you to worry.
Everyone's talking about you
here at the hospital.
So I wanted to see what happened
when I did some fortune telling,
and there was an ominous shadow
of a woman that came up.
Are you with a girl right now?
N-No, I'm not.
Hm?
Are you telling the truth?
I'm not lying.
Then can I check?
S-Sure.
But how?
I didn't think you'd actually come.
I got permission to go outside.
Weren't you supposed to be alone?
Oh, well, I said I wasn't with a girl,
but I didn't say I was alone.
Nice to meet you, Karen-chan.
I'm Emile Crossfode, Hayato's roommate.
You're male, correct?
O-Of course.
I'm going to get to the point.
Do you...
...like other men?
Hey, Karen!
So you two are really just roommates, then.
You're not trying to seduce
my brother or something, right?
O-Oh, come on.
Why would I? I'm a guy.
Well, I guess I'll leave it at that for now,
but I won't forgive you if you try
to do something to my brother.
Roar. Roar roar!
It's Sakura-san!
Sakura-san?
Yeah, it's the idol, Kirishima Sakura-san.
I listened to her songs
in the hospital today.
She's really popular right now.
I love her.
They're calling her the Diva of the World.
There's supposed to be an outdoor concert
on the Zwei Island chain today.
The Zwei Islands are pretty close
to our current position.
That's so cool!
I wanna go.
Let's go sometime.
Yeah! It's a promise.
Oh, yeah! I completely forgot.
What should we get for lunch?
Oh, Nii-san,
I have a place I want to go.
A place you want to go...
The cafeteria?
Yes. I've always wanted to come.
What should I get?
Salisbury steak, fried shrimp,
potstickers, curry rice,
stir-fried burdock, and...
Hey, you're going to get sick.
But everything on the menu looks good...
Don't tell Miharu, okay?
If you don't finish it all,
I'll eat it for you.
I'll be fine.
I'm going to have Nii-san eat it for me.
Hmph.
This is so good.
The food at the hospital is good, too,
but this is different.
You can have some of my
pasta too, if you want.
How is it?
It's great!
B-But this isn't enough to
get on my good side, okay?
What are you saying?
Oh, Kisaragi Hayato.
President.
President?
So that blonde with the drills is the one
who put you through all of that?
Hey, Karen!
I already heard her.
Who is that rude girl?
Sorry, this is my...
She's Kisaragi Karen.
Hayato-sama's little sister,
Claire-sama.
Pleased to meet you.
I am Claire-sama's assistant,
Chris Steinbelt, middle school second-year.
Oh, nice to meet you.
This is good timing.
I actually have something
to talk to you about.
Something to talk about?
Yes.
I want you to help out the student council.
Huh?
Hold on a second.
Why does Hayato have to help out with that?
The duel yesterday should have
been settled with that tie.
There's no obligation for him
to do as you say.
Calm down.
Of course it's not compulsory.
He's simply being recruited.
Huh?
Kisaragi Hayato,
I would like you to join Selections,
a special unit under the student council.
Selections?
You would follow orders from Warslarn HQ,
who manage the Little Garden.
You would remain a student but execute
missions like a full-fledged Slayer would.
The missions would include the guarding
of various facilities, bodyguard duties,
and of course, actual combat with Savages.
Combat...
Due to the Savage nest
elimination mission the other day,
we don't have enough Slayers.
We require immediate reinforcements.
Just as Liddy said,
this is not compulsory.
However, I believe in
noblesse oblige!
Those with power
should wield it
for the sake of those without it.
But I don't think I...
Then I will join with Hayato.
You do not meet the requirements.
You have to be able to
fight head-on with a Savage.
Or you'd drag everyone down.
So, you want me to face
the president in a duel, too?
How disrespectful, Emile Crossfode!
What can you do?!
It doesn't have to be the president.
Liddy Steinberg, I wouldn't mind
taking you on either.
That should be enough
to show you my abilities.
Damn you...
When do you want to have the duel?
I'm ready to go right now.
Hundred On.
A dragoon type?
Now, Vice President...
are you in or not?
Know your place.
Hundred On.
Liddy, stop it.
Don't stop me, Erica.
I need to put him in his place,
or it'll set a bad precedent.
Now things are getting interesting.
Stop it, Emile!
Don't go off firing around here!
Karen's here!
I know.
Then how about this?
She changed the form of her armament?!
Here I go!
Stop it!
I'll stop you with force.
Let them continue.
Claire-sama.
What?
Weren't you supposed to put me in my place?!
Don't get so cocky!
What?
An alert?
Claire-sama, we have an order to sortie.
Right.
Let's go, Liddy.
Looks like I don't have a choice.
You got out of this one.
Oh, you're going to run?
That's not it.
Something more important came up
than fighting you. That's all.
President! What's going on?
We have an emergency.
We received word that the Savage
have appeared on the Zwei Islands.
The Zwei Islands?
The place where Sakura-san was to perform.
Kisaragi Hayato...
I'll come to get your response
on joining Selections later.
Wait a second, Claire Harvey.
Charlotte Dimandius!
Take them with you.
What was that?
Hayato-kun, looks like you'll be
getting your first real battle.
Are you ready to participate?
A real battle...
A real battle with the Savage.
Variant Awakening